const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'πολύς',
    answers: ['veel'],
    explanation: '(polygaam, polyglot)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'μέγας',
    answers: ['groot'],
    explanation: '(megabyte, megafoon, omega, megalomanie)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'εἷς μία ἕν',
    answers: ['een', 'één'],
    explanation: '(hendiadys)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'οὐδείς',
    answers: ['niemand'],
    explanation: '(bij de indicatief)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'μηδείς',
    answers: ['niemand'],
    explanation: '(behalve bij indicatief)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δύο',
    answers: ['twee'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τρεῖς',
    answers: ['drie'],
    explanation: '(triteïsme)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τρία',
    answers: ['drie'],
    explanation: '(triteïsme)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τέσσαρες',
    answers: ['vier'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πέντε',
    answers: ['vijf'],
    explanation: '(pentagon, Pentateuch)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἕξ',
    answers: ['zes'],
    explanation: '(hexameter, hexaan)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἑπτά',
    answers: ['zeven'],
    explanation: '(heptarchie, heptameter)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δέκα',
    answers: ['tien'],
    explanation: '(decaloog)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δώδεκα',
    answers: ['twaalf'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τεσσαράκοντα',
    answers: ['veertig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἕκατον',
    answers: ['honderd'],
    explanation: '(hectogram)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'χιλιάς',
    answers: ['duizendtal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἑκατοντάρχης',
    answers: ['honderdman'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'χιλίαρχος',
    answers: ['militaire tribuun', 'aanvoerder van een cohorte', 'chiliarch'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson32Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson32-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 32 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson32Vocabulary
